[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["late night"]}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Why did do you this?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "do", "you", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "You know, it actually started by a late night conversation over twitter with a woman who was pooh-poohing government's role in provision nutrition for kids.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "actually", "started", "by", "a", "late", "night", "conversation", "over", "twitter", "with", "a", "woman", "who", "was", "pooh-poohing", "government", "'s", "role", "in", "provision", "nutrition", "for", "kids", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "How are you finding it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "finding", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "You know, it's a little more difficult than I imagined and I thought I would be good on eating on a tight budget.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "little", "more", "difficult", "than", "I", "imagined", "and", "I", "thought", "I", "would", "be", "good", "on", "eating", "on", "a", "tight", "budget", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "Your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "First of all, I hope people are sniping.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "I", "hope", "people", "are", "sniping", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "There is a real venomous (ph) disconnect here, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["There", "is", "a", "real", "venomous", "(", "ph", ")", "disconnect", "here", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", ":"], "qSentId": 133, "question": "Where do I send the Starbucks on Monday morning when it's all over for you?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "I", "send", "the", "Starbucks", "on", "Monday", "morning", "when", "it", "'s", "all", "over", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "I'm trying to decide whether having worked through days of headaches, whether I should go intravenous caffeine right away or stay away from this succulently seductive, addictive thing that --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "trying", "to", "decide", "whether", "having", "worked", "through", "days", "of", "headaches", ",", "whether", "I", "should", "go", "intravenous", "caffeine", "right", "away", "or", "stay", "away", "from", "this", "succulently", "seductive", ",", "addictive", "thing", "that", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Monday"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Starbucks"], "TIME": ["morning"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", ":", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "So he wasn't a leader until you needed leadership?", "question_tokens": ["So", "he", "was", "n't", "a", "leader", "until", "you", "needed", "leadership", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Maybe until -- maybe until he was presented with a stark opportunity to lead.", "answer_tokens": ["Maybe", "until", "--", "maybe", "until", "he", "was", "presented", "with", "a", "stark", "opportunity", "to", "lead", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "I'm sure Mayor Cory Booker has a lot to say about this, because he may be your rival, of course, should you -- you can confirm this now -- but should you come up against Chris Christie politically, what do you make of what's going on with him and the president?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "sure", "Mayor", "Cory", "Booker", "has", "a", "lot", "to", "say", "about", "this", ",", "because", "he", "may", "be", "your", "rival", ",", "of", "course", ",", "should", "you", "--", "you", "can", "confirm", "this", "now", "--", "but", "should", "you", "come", "up", "against", "Chris", "Christie", "politically", ",", "what", "do", "you", "make", "of", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "with", "him", "and", "the", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", ":", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "Well, first of all, I think that's the way government should work and that's what we should expect from people.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "the", "way", "government", "should", "work", "and", "that", "'s", "what", "we", "should", "expect", "from", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Cory Booker", "Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "Booker v. Christie 2013?", "question_tokens": ["Booker", "v.", "Christie", "2013", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "CC", "NNP", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "I'm not even going to give you the denial.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "even", "going", "to", "give", "you", "the", "denial", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Christie 2013"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "Could you beat him?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "beat", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "Look, I think he's vulnerable.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "vulnerable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "How would you feel if the president comes down and puts his arm around him again at the height of the battle?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "feel", "if", "the", "president", "comes", "down", "and", "puts", "his", "arm", "around", "him", "again", "at", "the", "height", "of", "the", "battle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "CC", "NNS", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "I think if there was a cause, a need for that, I applaud my president.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "if", "there", "was", "a", "cause", ",", "a", "need", "for", "that", ",", "I", "applaud", "my", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "WP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "Booker for Senate, 2013?", "question_tokens": ["Booker", "for", "Senate", ",", "2013", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Again, my focus right now is trying to figure out what that next step will be that is in accordance with my values.", "answer_tokens": ["Again", ",", "my", "focus", "right", "now", "is", "trying", "to", "figure", "out", "what", "that", "next", "step", "will", "be", "that", "is", "in", "accordance", "with", "my", "values", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2013"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Senate"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States of America"]}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "President of the New Jersey \"Star Trek\" association?", "question_tokens": ["President", "of", "the", "New", "Jersey", "``", "Star", "Trek", "''", "association", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Of the United States of America.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "the", "United", "States", "of", "America", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Jersey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "What do we actually know about this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "we", "actually", "know", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Well, I can sure you, Piers, no one is snickering or laughing tonight.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "can", "sure", "you", ",", "Piers", ",", "no", "one", "is", "snickering", "or", "laughing", "tonight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "EX", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "We don't actually know for sure, I guess at this stage, whether her death is 100 percent linked to what happened, do we?", "question_tokens": ["We", "do", "n't", "actually", "know", "for", "sure", ",", "I", "guess", "at", "this", "stage", ",", "whether", "her", "death", "is", "100", "percent", "linked", "to", "what", "happened", ",", "do", "we", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "WP", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "No, because we don't know the background, we don't know -- there might have been a series of events that culminated in her suicide but were not solely linked to this.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "because", "we", "do", "n't", "know", "the", "background", ",", "we", "do", "n't", "know", "--", "there", "might", "have", "been", "a", "series", "of", "events", "that", "culminated", "in", "her", "suicide", "but", "were", "not", "solely", "linked", "to", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "What do you make of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "Well, suicides are very complicated.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "suicides", "are", "very", "complicated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "What should be done about this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "should", "be", "done", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "That's such a difficult question.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "such", "a", "difficult", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Quickly, Kristen -- I'll come to you in a moment, Joe -- but do you feel comfortable that the Republicans are prepared to slash investment in something like food stamps in an effort to try and protect -- as it seems to many people -- the wealthiest 2 percent from paying more tax?", "question_tokens": ["Quickly", ",", "Kristen", "--", "I", "'ll", "come", "to", "you", "in", "a", "moment", ",", "Joe", "--", "but", "do", "you", "feel", "comfortable", "that", "the", "Republicans", "are", "prepared", "to", "slash", "investment", "in", "something", "like", "food", "stamps", "in", "an", "effort", "to", "try", "and", "protect", "--", "as", "it", "seems", "to", "many", "people", "--", "the", "wealthiest", "2", "percent", "from", "paying", "more", "tax", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", ":", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", ":", "JJ", "JJS", "CD", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "So I would disagree with the premise a little bit.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "I", "would", "disagree", "with", "the", "premise", "a", "little", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kristen", "Joe"], "PERCENT": ["2 percent"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 20 years"]}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "Where does that leave the party in four years time, if they try and fight on another platform that doesn't fully support and embrace gay rights in America?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "does", "that", "leave", "the", "party", "in", "four", "years", "time", ",", "if", "they", "try", "and", "fight", "on", "another", "platform", "that", "does", "n't", "fully", "support", "and", "embrace", "gay", "rights", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VB", "CC", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "Public opinion on this issue has changed very rapidly in sort of just the last 20 years.", "answer_tokens": ["Public", "opinion", "on", "this", "issue", "has", "changed", "very", "rapidly", "in", "sort", "of", "just", "the", "last", "20", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "How have you been?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "you", "been", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "I've been great.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "been", "great", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "But do you ever stop and think wow, I'm still only 33 and yet I've had this 18-year career?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "ever", "stop", "and", "think", "wow", ",", "I", "'m", "still", "only", "33", "and", "yet", "I", "'ve", "had", "this", "18-year", "career", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VB", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "CD", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "It's pretty unbelievable.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "pretty", "unbelievable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "What's being a mother like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "being", "a", "mother", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "Oh my God.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "my", "God", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Or had she just got lost in the maelstrom of fame and abuse and all the rest of it?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "had", "she", "just", "got", "lost", "in", "the", "maelstrom", "of", "fame", "and", "abuse", "and", "all", "the", "rest", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "One of the things that I can't -- I can't put my mind around is where she really was because, you know, at the end of her life, I wasn't there.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "of", "the", "things", "that", "I", "ca", "n't", "--", "I", "ca", "n't", "put", "my", "mind", "around", "is", "where", "she", "really", "was", "because", ",", "you", "know", ",", "at", "the", "end", "of", "her", "life", ",", "I", "was", "n't", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "IN", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "As somebody who still can, do you understand what that feeling must be like?", "question_tokens": ["As", "somebody", "who", "still", "can", ",", "do", "you", "understand", "what", "that", "feeling", "must", "be", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "WP", "RB", "MD", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "IN", "VBG", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "I understand what that feels like.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "understand", "what", "that", "feels", "like", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "How did you hear it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "hear", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "I was actually in the same hotel that she passed in.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "actually", "in", "the", "same", "hotel", "that", "she", "passed", "in", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "At the Beverly Hilton?", "question_tokens": ["At", "the", "Beverly", "Hilton", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Beverly Hilton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "It hit you that bad?", "question_tokens": ["It", "hit", "you", "that", "bad", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "It just hit me in ways I can't even explain.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "just", "hit", "me", "in", "ways", "I", "ca", "n't", "even", "explain", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "How is Ray doing, because he was very close to her?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "Ray", "doing", ",", "because", "he", "was", "very", "close", "to", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "VBG", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "Ray has been going through it.", "answer_tokens": ["Ray", "has", "been", "going", "through", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "Are you excited about having a new album out now, with everything that you've been through in the last 10 years?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "excited", "about", "having", "a", "new", "album", "out", "now", ",", "with", "everything", "that", "you", "'ve", "been", "through", "in", "the", "last", "10", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 10 years?"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121207pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "When you sing, what do you feel?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "sing", ",", "what", "do", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "I feel everything.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "everything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]